Subtitledtrailers.com
My name is Wade Watts.
My dad picked the name because
it sounded like a superhero's alter ego.
Like Peter Parker
or Bruce Banner.
But he died when I was a kid.
My mom, too.
And I ended up here.
Sitting here my tiny corner
of nowhere.
There's nowhere left to go,
nowhere,
except the OASIS.
A whole virtual universe.
People come to the OASIS
for all the things they can do.
But they stay
because of all the things
they can be.
Can you feel this?
Yeah.
It's the only place that feels
like I mean anything.
The OASIS was the brainchild
of James Halliday.
Hello.
If you're watching this, I'm dead.
I created a hidden object,
an easter egg.
The first person to find the egg
will inherit half a trillion dollars
and total control
of the OASIS itself.
Who is this, Parzival?
And how the hell is he winning?
Find him.
This isn't just a game.
I'm talking about
actual life-and-death stuff.
The OASIS,
the world's most important
economic resource.
It's nothing less than a war
for control of the future.
Welcome to the rebellion, Wade.
Like many of you people,
I only came here to escape.
But I found something much bigger
than just myself.
Are you willing to fight?
Help us save the OASIS.